streetarticles.com 2016-06-27

# Street Articles - Where Writers Become Authors

At Street Articles We take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**What This Privacy Policy Covers**

This policy covers how StreetArticles.com treats personal information that StreetArticles.com collects and receives, including information related to your past use of StreetArticles.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that StreetArticles.com does not own or control, or to people that StreetArticles.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**

StreetArticles.com collects personal information when you register with StreetArticles.com, when you use StreetArticles.com products or services, when you visit StreetArticles.com pages or the pages of certain StreetArticles.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. StreetArticles.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name and email address. Once you register with StreetArticles.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. StreetArticles.com collects information about your transactions with us.

StreetArticles.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, StreetArticles.com cookie information, and the page you request.

StreetArticles.com uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

StreetArticles.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission.

We transfer information about you if StreetArticles.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, StreetArticles.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Cookies**

StreetArticles.com may set and access StreetArticles.com cookies on your computer.

**Confidentiality and Security**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
